Ceará, Brasil

【 (+55) 85-99713-0901 | ■ dyegoaurelio@gmail.com | ☑ dyegoaurelio | Ⅲ dyegoaurelio

Skills_

DevOps Docker - Azure - GitHub Actions - Nginx **Programming** Python - Typescript - Javascript - Bash

Front-end React - Next.js - Redux - React - Vite - HTML5 - CSS

Back-end Flask - Django - FastApi - Express.js - MySQL - PostgreSQL - MongoDB

Data Science Pandas - Power Bi

About

I'm extremely passionate about programming, web development and Linux. I've worked with many full stack technologies, mostly using Typescript and Python. I also love learning new technologies and aim to work with web security in the future. I'm a great problem solver and can work with agile environments.

I'm a open source enthusiast, love to contribute whenever I'm able to, and also discover all kinds of open source projects.

Experience

Pax Insurance Broker Ceará, Brazil

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Mar. 2021 - Present

- Developed a system to manage costumer's Health Insurance changes
- Creation of Power Bi panels for business presentations
- Developed a database to store all costumer's data
- Development of various systems in order to automate many company's internal processes using Python ans Pandas

Mobills Ceará, Brazil

Mar. 2021 - Dec. 2021 FRONTEND DEVELOPER

- Worked on many new features, refactors and bug fixes on Mobills web platform, using React, Redux and Redux Saga
- Personalized Zendesk templates using Vanilla JS and CSS for Mobills Help Center

Languages_

English Advanced Portuguese Native

Education

UFC(Federal University of Ceará)

Ceará, Brazil RENEWABLE ENERGY ENGINEERING

2018 - Now